Guide to the Papers of Rev. Richards A. Zariņš, 1883-2008 M1938
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6. The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church of New York and congregation
  - Ladies Aid Committee
    - The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church in America (LELBA), East Coast. Conferences of Ladies Aid Committees, 1973-1978 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church in America (LELBA), East Coast. Conferences of Ladies Aid Committees, 1979, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church in America (LELBA), East Coast. Conferences of Ladies Aid Committees, 1983, 1985, 1989, 1994, 1995, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Social assistance. Care for the elderly
    - Church Assistance Fund. Care for sick parishioners: financial reports, correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Church Assistance Fund: announcements, financial reports, correspondence, 1953-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Church Assistance Fund: announcements, financial reports, correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Care organization for elderly "Celsme": regulations, announcements, correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Pension Fund and related materials, 1979-1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Care for military servicemen: correspondence, leaflets, 1952-1965 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Youth activities
    - Sunday schools: minutes of meetings, announcements, correspondence, 1948-1956 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Sunday schools: minutes of meetings, school regulations, announcements, financial reports, correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Sunday schools: minutes of meetings, announcements, school regulations, 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Sunday schools: reports, school regulations, announcements, correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Sunday schools: minutes of meetings, announcements, circulars, 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Sunday schools: circulars, announcements, lists of students, 1967-1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Sunday schools: religious instruction, announcements, reports, 1975-1998 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Scouts and guides: reports, announcements, correspondence, 1949-1993 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Youth Club, The Latvian American Youth Association and related materials: reports, announcements of events, correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Youth Circle, The Latvian American Youth Association and related materials: reports, announcements of events, correspondence, 1954-1970 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Latvian students' organizations: circulars, correspondence 1950-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Children's summer camp: parishioners' donations: lists, correspondence, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Children's summer camp: looking for property: correspondence, leaflets, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Children's summer camp in Catskills: circulars, announcements, clippings, 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Children's summer camp in Catskills: circulars, announcements, reports, leaflets, 1961-1970 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Children's summer camp in Catskills: circulars, announcements, clippings, 1977-1995 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cultural and social life
    - The parish choir: concert programs, announcements, reports, clippings, 1947-1951 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - The parish choir: concert programs, announcements, reports, clippings, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - The parish choir: conductor Bruno Skulte, 1905-1976: concert programs, announcements, clippings, correspondence, 1949-1965 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - The parish choir: conductor Bruno Skulte, 1905-1976: concert programs, announcements, clippings, correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Latvian Song Festivals: programs, leaflets, correspondence, 1953-1973 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - History of Latvian musical life in New York: programs (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Latvian musical life in New York: programs, clippings, correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Latvian musical life in New York: programs, clippings, correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Latvian musical life in New York: programs, clippings, correspondence, 1974- programs, clippings, correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Latvian musical life in New York: opera singer Elza Zebranska, 1903-1996: articles, clippings, programs (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Latvian musical life in New York: programs, clippings, correspondence, 1974-1999 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Theater and literary events: programs, correspondence, research papers, 1950-1996 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Latvian artists and art exhibits in New York: programs, correspondence, clippings, 1951-1989 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Latvian painter Ludolfs Liberts, 1895-1959: programs of exhibits, correspondence, clippings (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Paintings: the property of congregation (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - The Library: lists, reports, correspondence, clippings, 1950-1964 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - The Library: lists, reports, correspondence, clippings, 1965-1994 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Loyalty Parades with Latvian participation: announcements, correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Celebration of Latvian Independence Day, November 18: programs, announcements, 1934-2001 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Recreational trips: lists of participants, leaflets, 1950-1951 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Latvian organizations in exile
    - New York Latvian Society. History: Statutes, programs, announcements, 1928-1940 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - New York Latvian Society. History: programs, announcements, 1941-1945 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - New York Latvian Society. History: notes, manuscripts, clippings (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - New York Latvian Society. Financial overviews, 1938-1973, 1984, 1997, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - New York Latvian Society. Excerpts from the minutes of meetings, 1947-1952 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - New York Latvian Society: announcements, programs, 1946-1950 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - New York Latvian Society: announcements, programs, 1951-1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - New York Latvian Society: announcements, programs and related materials, 1959-1967 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - New York Latvian Society: announcements, programs, 1968-1974 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - New York Latvian Society: a 100 year anniversary: correspondence, manuscripts, programs, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Latvian Nationality Conference Committee: correspondence, reports, 1947-1948 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - United American Latvian Council of New York: correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Council of American Latvian Organizations of New York, Inc.: correspondence, reports, 1965-1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Latvian Consultative Panel: correspondence, reports, speeches, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Committee for a Free Latvia: correspondence, statements, 1951-1953 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Latvian American Association of University Professors and Instructors, Inc. (LAMSA) and related materials: booklets, clippings, correspondence, 1950-1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - American Latvian Association (ALA): correspondence, circulars, congressional ptotocols, 1950-1959 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - American Latvian Association: correspondence, circulars, congressional ptotocols, 1960-1998 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - American Latvian Association. Cultural Bureau: correspondence, circulars, reports, 1951-1968 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - American Latvian Association. Latvian Institute: correspondence, circulars, reports, 1979-1998 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - American Latvian Association. Care Office: circulars, reports, 1951-1960 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Daugavas Vanagi in New York: correspondence, circulars, booklet, 1955-2000 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Baltic unity. Baltic States Freedom Committee and related materials: programs, leaflets, 1948-1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Baltic unity. Baltic Appeal to the United Nations (BATUN) and related materials: news releases, statements, correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous organizations and political activities: statements, news releases, clippings, correspondence, 1949-1986 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Cooperative Committe for Suport of Deportees: reports, lists of donations, 1962-1967 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Series 7. Collected material of contemporaries
  - Ādamsons, Miervaldis, 1910-1946: biography (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Bāliņš, Adolfs, 1896-: memoirs (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Balodis, Nikolajs, 1901-1991: personal documents (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Balodis, Nikolajs, 1901-1991: personal documents, correspondence (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Balodis, Nikolajs, 1901-1991: personal documents, correspondence, photographs (Box 73, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of correspondence with Hugo Štrauss and Milda Grimma-Štrauss, Ziedonis un Milda Landavs, Magda Stotts etc.
  - Balodis, Nikolajs, 1901-1991: photographs (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Bārda, Paulis, 1901-1991: biography, correspondence, manuscripts (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Berkolds, Arturs, 1902-1959: personal documents (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Bērzups, Olga, 1899-1999: 100 birthday celebration's materials (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Biezais, Haralds, 1906-1995: publications in journals, reviews, correspondence, clippings (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Bļodnieks, Arvīds: biography (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Blumbergs, Osvalds. Blumberga, Emma: programs, a photograph (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Bošs, Ilmārs, 1912-1997: biography (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Boževskis, Jete, 1903-1990. Boževskis, Antons, 1901-1974: personal documents (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Celms, Teodors, 1893-1989: The lecures delivered at Riga University in 1943/44: Methodology of science (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Danzis, Gustavs, 1868-1953: correspondence, postcards, announcements (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Danzis, Gustavs, 1868-1953: miscellaneous documents (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Dīriķis, Leo, 1873-1959: autobiography, personal papers (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Dīkmanis, Harijs, 1895-1979: biography, correspondence (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Dombrovskis, Gustavs, 1892- :biography (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Dombrovskis, Raimonds: biography, clippings (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Druva, Elija, 1895-1993: materials for biograpfy, correspondence, clippings (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Dzintars, Jānis, 1907: personal documents (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Fetler, Daniel, 1914-1995: correspondence: materials on lawsuit (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Grava Uldis, Grava, Sarmīte: correspondence, family history (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Grendze-Kamols, Olga: correspondence, materials about the book (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Indrihsons, Heinrihs, 1902- personal documents, biography (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Jaunzemis, Atis, 1893-1940?: biography (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Jordāns, Oskars, 1901-1977: materials for biography (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Juškevičs, Lilija, 1898-1964: personal documents (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Kalniņš, Nikolajs, 1911-2001: poems, clippings (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Kalvis-Kalvijaka, Vilhelmine, 1888-1984: biography (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Kihss, Peter, 1880-: correspondence, cards (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Klaips, Bruno, 1912-1994: personal documents (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Kļaviņš, Helene, 1899-1995: personal documents, correspondence (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Klints, Bernhards, 1890- biography (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Klīve, Visvaldis, 1931-2003: manuscripts, discussion materials (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Krēsliņš, Jānis, 1924-: correspondence, clippings of his articles (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Krieviņš, Voldemārs, 1896-1965: biography (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Ķezbere, Elza, 1911-2011: poetry, correspondence, clippings (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Kūlītis, Alfreds: biography, published article (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Līdacis, Arvīds, 1914-2005: his publications (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Moors, Helēna, 1906-: biography (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Niedze (Needse)-Sauleskalns, Vilhelmine (Mīce), 1887-1972: personal documents, materials for biography, rehersal material (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Niedze (Needse)-Sauleskalns, Vilhelmine (Mīce), 1887-1972: correspondence, post cards (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Niedze (Needse)-Sauleskalns, Vilhelmine (Mīce), 1887-1972: correspondence on post cards (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Niedze (Needse),Vilhelmine (Mīce),1887-1972. Niedze, Ludis: correspondence on post cards, blank cards (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Niedze (Needse),Vilhelmine (Mīce),1887-1972: photographs (Box 75, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of photographs: the first years of Mīce Ilmers in New York, marriage to Jānis Sauleskalns, choir activities, Latvian orchestra, friends: mostly unidentified
  - Niedze (Needse),Vilhelmine (Mīce),1887-1972: photographs (Box 75, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of photographs: MIce's marriage to Ludis Niedze, choir activities, Latvian theater, friends: mostly unidentified
  - Niedze (Needse),Vilhelmine (Mīce),1887-1972: photographs (Box 75, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of photographs: Later years, from 1938, MIce's marriage to Ludis Niedze, Latvian theater, friends: mostly unidentified. Mice's marriage to E. Schoonmaker
  - Plūmanis, Kārlis, 1892-1990: autobiography (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Prince, Auguste, 1904-1995: materials for biography (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Rauza, Ida, 1904-1985: personal documents (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Riekstiņš, Jānis: biography (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Ruņģis, Marta, 1900-1989: personal documents (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Sloka, Lauma, 1891-1960: biograohy (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Robert, 1885-1957: correspondence, materials for biography (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Sole, William, 1894-1947: biography (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Sprincis, Alfreds, 1906-2002: memoirs, biography (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Stankevičs, Kārlis, 1892-1980: materials for biography, photographs (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Steiks, Pēteris, 1879-1957. Steiks, Jānis, 1855-1932: memoirs, materials for biography, clippings (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Šteinberga, Austra, 1910-1998: materials for biography (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Stots, Eduards: materials for biography (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Strazdiņa, Anna, 1895-1980: personal papers (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Zariņš, Zemvalds, 1921-: immigration documents, correspondence (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Zīle, Lizete, 1896-: personal and immigration documents (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Zīle, Kārlis, 1897-: personal and immigration documents (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Zutis, Vilma, 1914-1992: correspondence, materials for biography (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified: private diary, 1944-1945 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Series 8. Research file on the history of The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia
  - General history of The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia: notes, manuscripts, articles (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Lists of pastors in Latvia, 1853-1952; 1989 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Documents: confirmation documents, funeral service leaflets etc., 1920-1996 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - The martyrs of The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia: lists, notes, printed articles, 1918-1920 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia under Soviet rule: manuscripts, notes, correspondence, 1944-1957 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Lutheran Churches in Latvia: materials for the album: manuscripts, correspondence, notes, photographs, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia under Soviet rule: manuscripts, notes, correspondence, news releases, 1958-1968 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Archbishop Gustavs Turs, 1890-1973: correspondence, clippings, news releases (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia under Soviet rule: manuscripts, notes, correspondence, news releases, 1969-2000 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church in Exile: lists of pastors, addresses, 1946-1959 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Pastors of The Evangelical Lutheran Church of Latvia and of The Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church in Exile: biographies (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - History of Christianity. Martin Luter and Baltic region: notes, booklets, clippings (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - History of Christianity. Martin Luter and Baltic region: notes, booklets, clippings (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - History of Christianity. Martin Luter and Baltic region: notes, booklets, clippings (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Christian humour (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Series 9. Research file on history of Latvia
  - History of Latvia in the 20th century: copies of articles and related materials (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - History of Latvia in the 20th century: copies of articles and related materials (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Latvians in different countries: copies of articles (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Series 10. Research file on the history of early Latvian theater and the societies in New York and other cities
  - The Lettish Educational Society of New York: theater programs, announcements, 1922-1928 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - The Lettish Educational Society of New York: theater programs, announcements, 1929-1934 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Cīņas Biedri, New York: theater programs, announcements, 1922-1934 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - The Society of Latvian Christian Men, New York: announcements, programs of events, 1940-1943 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - The Latvian Club of Newark, New Jersey: theater programs, announcements, 1924-1930 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - The Latvian Library Society, New York: announcements of different events, 1928 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - The Latvian Branch of International Labor Defense, New York: theater programs, announcements, 1924-1935 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - The Latvian Branch of International Labor Defense, New York: theater programs, announcements, 1936-1940 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - The Latvian Workers' Club, New York: theater programs, announcements, 1933-1934 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - The Latvian Worker's Club, New York: theater programs, announcements, 1933-1934 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Other Latvian societies and clubs in New York: announcements of different events, programs, 1923-1947 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - The Latvian Workers' Society, Chicago: theater programs, announcements, 1924-1934 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - The Latvian Workers' Society, Chicago: theater programs, announcements, 1934-1937 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - The Illinois Latvian Benevolent Society: different programms, announcements, 1935-1947 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - The Philadelphia Society of Free Letts: different programs, announcements, 1922-1943 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - The Philadelphia Latvian Educational Society "Prometejs": different programs, announcements (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - The Latvian Women's Club, Chicago: programms, announcements, 1928-1936 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - The Philadelphia Latvian Council of Progressive Organizations: different programs, announcements, 1924-1934 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - The Latvian Workers' Society, Boston: programs of events, 1923-1937 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Series 11. Printed material
  - Clippings
    - Lutheran Church in Latvia and in emigration, 1947-1979 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Lutheran Church in Latvia and in emigration, 1980-1999 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Church events around the world, 1955-2000 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Cultural and political events in Latvia and in emigration, 1951-1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Cultural and political events in Latvia and in emigration, 1970-2000 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Cultural and political events in Latvia and in emigration, 1970-2000 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Culture and politics in the United States (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook: articles related to Latvian community in the United States (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Calendars
    - Ihstais tautas kalendars 1884. gadam. Riga, 1883 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Amerikas Latweeschu Luteranu kalendars 1906. gadam, 1912. gadam, 1914. gadam. Bostona, published by J. Sieberg (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Latwijas Kulturas Weizinaschanas Beedriba. Gada grahmata 1922. gadam. 1. gada gahjums. Riga, 1921 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - "Jaunās Balss" Tautas kalendārs 1926. gadam. Rīga, 1925 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Gada grāmata Neatkarīgais Vārds 1927. gadam. Rīga, 1926 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Amerikas Latweeschu Strahdneeku kalendars 1929. gadam. Bostona, 1928 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Latviešu apgādu gada grāmata 1948. gadam. Detmolda, North-Rine-Westphalia, Germany, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Tēvijas kalendārs 1950. gadam, 1955. gadam. Dillingen and Memmingen, Bavaria, Germany. Published by Eduards Alainis (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Latviešu almanachs 1956. gadam. London, 1955. Published by Arturs Bērziņš (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Baznīcas kalendārs 1944. gadam. 1. daļa. Rīga, 1943. Editor, Richards Zariņš (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Baznīcas kalendārs 1947.-1948. gadam. Rīga (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Baznīcas kalendārs 1954.-1961. gadam. Rīga (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Baznīcas kalendārs 1962.-1963., 1965., 1968.-1969., 1984. gadam. Rīga (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1949.-1951. Published in Gunzburg, Bavaria, Germany (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1952., 1955.-1956., 1957.-1959. Published in Glenview, Ill. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1960.-1963. Glenview, Ill. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1964.-1967. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1968.-1971. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas kalendārs, 1972. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1973-1974. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1975-1976. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1977-1978. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1979-1980. Glenview, Ill. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1981.-1982. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1983.-1984. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1985.-1986. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1987.-1988. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1989.-1990. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Latvijas Evanģeliski Luteriskās Baznīcas gada grāmata un kalendārs, 1991. Glenview, Ill. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Booklets
    Prepared by the Latvian members of the Baltic Committee for the Madison Square Garden Mass Rally on Nov. 13, 1965, in cooperation with Lithuanian and Estonian members
    - Mittheilungen des livländischen Generalsuperintendenten über das Kirchenwesen im Jahre 1902. Jurjew (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Amerikas latweeschu konkordijas rakstu-krahjums. Cambridgeport, Mass., 1906. Published by J. Sieberg (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Balodis, W.D. Jumeras leja in wiņas eewehrojamas weetas. Walmeera, 1909 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Uz Zeemas Swehtkeem. Riga, 1910 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Zaru Romanowu jubilejai. Brisele, 1910 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Latwijas walsts pasludinaschana, 18. nowembrî 1918. g.: rakstu wainags. Rīga, 1918 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Slawas Dseesmas. Ņujorka, 1919 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Amerikas Latweeschu Tautiskās Saweenibas Otrā kongresa protokols. Ņujorka, 1919 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Amerikas Latweeschu Tautiskās Saweenibas Treschais un Amerikas Latweeschu Pirmais kongress noturets 4, 5, un 6 septembrī, 1920. g. Ņujorkā. Ņujorka, 1920 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Steik, John. Latvia's Opera. New York, 1921 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - The Baltic republics: what they are, what they have. New York, 1922 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Biskapu eeweschanas swinibas Rīgā, 16. julijā 1922.g. Rīga, 1922 (Box 85, Folder 2)